<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="no"?>
<modDesc descVersion="53">
    <author>Edge Gaming</author>
    <version>1.0.0.0</version>
    <title><!-- en=English de=German jp=Japanese pl=Polish cz=Czech fr=French es=Spanish ru=Russian it=Italian pt=Portuguese hu=Hungary nl=Netherlands cs=Chinese (Simplified) ct=Chinese (Traditional) br=Brazilian-Portuguese tr=Turkish ro=Romanian kr=Korean -->
        <en>Gas Station Mod</en>
        <de>Tankstelle Mod</de>
        <fr>Station-service Mod</fr>
        <es>Mod de gasolinera</es>
        <ru>Мод АЗС</ru>
        <pl>Stacja benzynowa Mod</pl>
        <it>Stazione di servizio Mod</it>
    </title>
    <description>
        <en><![CDATA[A Stylish and sleek fuel pump for your farm, with underground Tank. You pay a 5% fee for delivery of fuel.
Its also connected to water so no more driving into rivers and lakes to fill up your water tanks. Water you get here also is free!!

-The building have automatic lighting.

--Technical Info--

EDGE Fuel Pump:
Price: 5.000€
Upkeep: 5€ Daily.
Size: 2.5 x 5 Meters.
FillTypes: Water, Diesel, Def.
Overloading Speed: Diesel 75 Liters Per Second, Water 500 Liters Per Second.

-Supports "Seasons" & "Courseplay Six".

-If you find any bugs or got suggestions for improvment, please dont hesitate to contact us on our Github page at https://github.com/FS19-Mods-By-EDGE/.
We also need help with getting our translations better, as well as getting it translated to more languages, this can also be done from there.]]></en>

<de><![CDATA[Noch eine Kraftstoffpumpe für Ihre Farm. mit unterirdischem Tank. Sie zahlen eine Gebühr von 5% für die Lieferung von Kraftstoff. Wasser kann auch hier bekommen werden und es ist kostenlos!

-Das Gebäude verfügt über eine automatische Beleuchtung.

--Technische Information--

EDGE Kraftstoffpumpe:
Preis: 5.000 €
Unterhalt: 5 € täglich.
Größe: 2,5 x 5 Meter.
Fülltypen: Wasser, Diesel.
Überladegeschwindigkeit: Diesel 75 Liter pro Sekunde, Wasser 500 Liter pro Sekunde.

-Unterstützt "Seasons" und "Courseplay Six" .

-Wenn Sie Fehler finden oder Verbesserungsvorschläge haben, zögern Sie bitte nicht, uns auf unserer Github-Seite unter https://github.com/FS19-Mods-By-EDGE/
We also need help with getting our translations better, as well as getting it translated to more languages, this can also be done from there.]]></de>

        <fr><![CDATA[Encore une autre pompe à carburant pour votre ferme. avec réservoir souterrain. Vous payez des frais de 5% pour la livraison de carburant. L'eau peut également être obtenue ici, et c'est gratuit!

-Le bâtiment dispose d'un éclairage automatique.

--Info technique--

Pompe à carburant EDGE:
Prix: 5.000 €
Entretien: 5 € par jour.
Taille: 2,5 x 5 mètres.
Types de remplissage: eau, diesel.
Vitesse de surcharge: Diesel 75 litres par seconde, eau 500 litres par seconde.

-Supporte "Seasons" & "Courseplay Six" .

-Si vous trouvez des bugs ou avez des suggestions d'amélioration, n'hésitez pas à nous contacter sur notre page Github à https://github.com/FS19-Mods-By-EDGE/
We also need help with getting our translations better, as well as getting it translated to more languages, this can also be done from there.]]></fr>

        <es><![CDATA[Otra bomba de combustible más para su granja. con tanque subterráneo. Paga una tarifa del 5% por la entrega de combustible. Aquí también se puede conseguir agua, ¡y es gratis!

-El edificio tiene iluminación automática.

--Información técnica--

Bomba de combustible EDGE:
Precio: 5.000 €
Mantenimiento: 5 € diario.
Tamaño: 2,5 x 5 metros.
FillTypes: agua, diesel.
Velocidad de sobrecarga: Diesel 75 litros por segundo, agua 500 litros por segundo.

-Soporta "Seasons" y "Courseplay Six".

-Si encuentra algún error u obtiene sugerencias de mejora, no dude en contactarnos en nuestra página de Github en https://github.com/FS19-Mods-By-EDGE/
We also need help with getting our translations better, as well as getting it translated to more languages, this can also be done from there.]]></es>

        <ru><![CDATA[Еще один топливный насос для вашей фермы. с подземным резервуаром. Вы платите 5% комиссию за доставку топлива. Воду тоже можно достать, причем бесплатно!

-В здании автоматическое освещение.

--Техническая информация--

Топливный насос EDGE:
Стоимость: 5.000 €
Содержание: 5 евро в день.
Размер: 2,5 х 5 метров.
Типы заливки: Вода, Дизель.
Скорость перегрузки: дизельное топливо 75 литров в секунду, вода 500 литров в секунду.

-Поддержка "Seasons" и "Courseplay Six".

-Если вы обнаружите какие-либо ошибки или получите предложения по улучшению, пожалуйста, не стесняйтесь связаться с нами на нашей странице Github по адресу https://github.com/FS19-Mods-By-EDGE/
We also need help with getting our translations better, as well as getting it translated to more languages, this can also be done from there.]]></ru>

        <pl><![CDATA[Kolejna pompa paliwowa dla Twojego gospodarstwa. z podziemnym zbiornikiem. Za dostawę paliwa płacisz 5% opłaty. Można tu również dostać wodę i jest za darmo!

-Budynek posiada automatyczne oświetlenie.

--Informacje techniczne--

EDGE Pompa paliwa:
Cena: 5.000 €
Koszt utrzymania: 5 € dziennie.
Rozmiar: 2,5 x 5 metrów.
Typy wypełnień: woda, olej napędowy.
Prędkość przeładowania: olej napędowy 75 litrów na sekundę, woda 500 litrów na sekundę.

-Obsługuje „Seasons” i „Courseplay Six”.

-Jeśli znajdziesz jakieś błędy lub masz sugestie dotyczące ulepszeń, nie wahaj się skontaktować z nami na naszej stronie Github pod adresem https://github.com/FS19-Mods-By-EDGE/
We also need help with getting our translations better, as well as getting it translated to more languages, this can also be done from there.]]></pl>
        <it><![CDATA[Ancora un'altra pompa del carburante per la tua fattoria. con cisterna interrata. Paghi una commissione del 5% per la consegna del carburante. L'acqua può anche essere presa qui ed è gratis!

-L'edificio dispone di illuminazione automatica.

--Informazioni tecniche--

Pompa carburante EDGE:
Prezzo: 5.000 €
Manutenzione: 5 € al giorno.
Dimensioni: 2,5 x 5 metri.
Tipi di riempimento: acqua, gasolio.
Velocità di sovraccarico: diesel 75 litri al secondo, acqua 500 litri al secondo.

-Supporta "Stagioni" e "Courseplay Six".

-Se trovi qualche bug o hai suggerimenti per l'improvvisazione, non esitare a contattarci sulla nostra pagina Github all'indirizzo https://github.com/FS19-Mods-By-EDGE/
We also need help with getting our translations better, as well as getting it translated to more languages, this can also be done from there.]]></it>
	</description>
    <iconFilename>GasStationMod_Icon.dds</iconFilename>
    <multiplayer supported="true"/>
    <storeItems>
        <storeItem rootNode="placeable" xmlFilename="data/GasStationMod.xml"/>
    </storeItems>
    <brands>
        <brand name="EDGE" title="EDGE Industries" image="store/EDGE_Brand_Logo.dds"/>
    </brands>
    <l10n>
        <text name="action_turnOnMarking">
            <en>Show warning Stripes</en>
            <de>Eckmarkierungen einblenden</de>
            <fr>Afficher les rayures d'avertissement</fr>
            <es>Mostrar franjas de advertencia</es>
            <ru>Показать предупреждение полосы</ru>
            <pl>Pokaż paski ostrzegawcze</pl>
            <it>Mostra strisce di avviso</it>
        </text>
        <text name="action_turnOffMarking">
            <en>Hide warning Stripes</en>
            <de>Eckmarkierungen ausblenden</de>
            <fr>Masquer les bandes d'avertissement</fr>
            <es>Ocultar rayas de advertencia</es>
            <ru>Скрыть предупреждение полосы</ru>
            <pl>Ukryj paski ostrzegawcze</pl>
            <it>Nascondi le strisce di avvertimento</it>
        </text>
        <text name="function_EDGELights">
            <en>This Building have Automatic Lighting.</en>
            <de>Dieses Gebäude verfügt über eine automatische Beleuchtung.</de>
            <fr>Ce bâtiment a l'éclairage automatique.</fr>
            <es>Este edificio tiene iluminación automática.</es>
            <ru>Это здание имеет автоматическое освещение.</ru>
            <pl>Ten budynek ma automatyczne oświetlenie.</pl>
            <it>Questo edificio ha l'illuminazione automatica.</it>
        </text>
        <text name="EDGENitro">
            <en>EDGE Nitro +</en>
        </text>
        <text name="name_EDGENitro">
            <en>EDGE Nitro Plus</en>
        </text>
        <text name="name_GasStationMod">
            <en>Fuel Pump</en>
            <de>Benzinpumpe</de>
            <fr>Pompe à carburant</fr>
            <es>Bomba de combustible</es>
            <ru>топливный насос</ru>
            <pl>Pompa paliwowa</pl>
            <it>Pompa di benzina</it>
        </text>
        <text name="function_GasStationMod">
            <en>A Stylish and sleek fuel pump for your farm, with underground Tank. You pay a 5% fee for delivery of fuel. It will also provide you with free water!</en>
            <de>Eine stilvolle und elegante Kraftstoffpumpe für Ihren Betrieb mit unterirdischem Tank. Sie zahlen eine Gebühr von 5% für die Lieferung von Kraftstoff. Es wird Ihnen auch kostenloses Wasser geben!</de>
            <fr>Une pompe à carburant élégante et élégante pour votre ferme, avec réservoir souterrain. Vous payez des frais de 5% pour la livraison de carburant. Il vous fournira également de l'eau gratuite!</fr>
            <es>Una bomba de combustible elegante y elegante para su granja, con tanque subterráneo. Paga una tarifa del 5% por la entrega de combustible. ¡También te proporcionará agua gratis!</es>
            <ru>Стильный и изящный топливный насос для вашей фермы с подземным баком. Вы платите 5% комиссию за доставку топлива. Он также предоставит вам бесплатную воду!</ru>
            <pl>Stylowa i elegancka pompa paliwa dla Twojego gospodarstwa z podziemnym zbiornikiem. Za dostawę paliwa płacisz 5% opłaty. Zapewni Ci również darmową wodę!</pl>
            <it>Una pompa del carburante elegante ed elegante per la tua fattoria, con serbatoio interrato. Paghi una commissione del 5% per la consegna del carburante. Ti fornirà anche acqua gratis!</it>
        </text>
    </l10n>
    <credits><![CDATA[
## Contributors
- Castiga, EDGE Gaming
## Translations
- Castiga
## Designers
- Castiga, EDGE Gaming]]></credits>
</modDesc>
